https://thunderridgeski.com/the-mountain/privacy

Privacy - Thunder Ridge Ski Area
COVID-19 UPDATES
Learn More
Call us at 845-878-4100
MenuThe MountainCOVID-19 UpdatesAbout UsConditionsContact UsDirectionsEmploymentHours of OperationSki ShopLodging & DiningLocal DiningLodgingMetro-NorthMountain CamMountain SafetyTerrain ParkTrail Map CloseLessons/RacingSnowsports SchoolDaily Group LessonsHalf-Day ProgramPrivate LessonsSix Week ProgramRacingRace Team InformationRacing News & Updates CloseTickets/Season PassesBuy OnlineGift CardsLift TicketsRental EquipmentSeason PassesTuning Services CloseDeals/EventsEventsSkiing with SantaCollege NightDiscounts at Other Ski AreasMid-Week SpecialsWine & Women WednesdaysSki ClubsFirst RespondersSeniors on the SlopesMilitary Active Duty and VeteransTuesday Night is Adult Game Night CloseGroups4th GradeGroup PackagesPhoto GalleryScout ProgramsMetro-North Close
MenuThe MountainCOVID-19 UpdatesAbout UsConditionsContact UsDirectionsEmploymentHours of OperationSki ShopLodging & DiningLocal DiningLodgingMetro-NorthMountain CamMountain SafetyTerrain ParkTrail Map CloseLessons/RacingSnowsports SchoolDaily Group LessonsHalf-Day ProgramPrivate LessonsSix Week ProgramRacingRace Team InformationRacing News & Updates CloseTickets/Season PassesBuy OnlineGift CardsLift TicketsRental EquipmentSeason PassesTuning Services CloseDeals/EventsEventsSkiing with SantaCollege NightDiscounts at Other Ski AreasMid-Week SpecialsWine & Women WednesdaysSki ClubsFirst RespondersSeniors on the SlopesMilitary Active Duty and VeteransTuesday Night is Adult Game Night CloseGroups4th GradeGroup PackagesPhoto GalleryScout ProgramsMetro-North Close
MenuThe MountainCOVID-19 UpdatesAbout UsConditionsContact UsDirectionsEmploymentHours of OperationSki ShopLodging & DiningLocal DiningLodgingMetro-NorthMountain CamMountain SafetyTerrain ParkTrail Map CloseLessons/RacingSnowsports SchoolDaily Group LessonsHalf-Day ProgramPrivate LessonsSix Week ProgramRacingRace Team InformationRacing News & Updates CloseTickets/Season PassesBuy OnlineGift CardsLift TicketsRental EquipmentSeason PassesTuning Services CloseDeals/EventsEventsSkiing with SantaCollege NightDiscounts at Other Ski AreasMid-Week SpecialsWine & Women WednesdaysSki ClubsFirst RespondersSeniors on the SlopesMilitary Active Duty and VeteransTuesday Night is Adult Game Night CloseGroups4th GradeGroup PackagesPhoto GalleryScout ProgramsMetro-North Close
Access for Seasonal Locker Holders is available by appointment. We look forward to the upcoming ski season!
lifts
0
trails
0
base
0"
View All Conditions
Privacy
Thunder Ridge Ski Area cares about your privacy. We want our customers to be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any we disclose it. This policy applies to the
Thunder Ridge Ski Area
web site as well as our secure site for making online purchases and internal sources for collecting mailing lists etc.
By providing
Thunder Ridge Ski Area with Personal Information you signify that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy policy as posted here. If you do not agree with any terms in this policy, please do not provide any Personal Information.
As used in this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information”, means personally identifiable information such as your name, street address, telephone number, date of birth, credit card information and email address. Credit card information is used for online purchasing exclusively and not retained in our database.
When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, which includes your right to limit our use of your Personal Information.
How we use your information:
When you supply us with your Personal Information we will use it for the express purpose for which it was collected (e.g., to enter you in a contest, future mailings, online orders, and email notifications). We do use your Personal Information to also mail
Thunder Ridge Ski Area information to you. At any time however, you may opt out of such by contacting Thunder Ridge Ski Area
at
845-878-4100 or by emailing us. Please place “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the subject and specify from which areas, email or regular mail, you wish to unsubscribe.
At times we may retain third parties to enable delivery or products or services. These third parties, including suppliers, are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any other way. Thunder Ridge Ski Area does not sell Personal Information.
Please note: We will release your Personal Information if required to do so by law or by search warrant, subpoena or court order.
Thunder Ridge Ski Area reserves the right to change our Privacy Policy at our discretion.
Mid-Week Specials!
Monday – Thursday, non-holiday!$30 lift, $30 rental, $30 lesson!
READ MORE
Ride the Ski Train
No car, no problem!  Ride the Ski Train from Grand Central Station in NYC.  Buy the Thunder Ski Package and take our free shuttle from the Patterson, NY train station.  Combo discounted round trip train ticket and lift ticket!
READ MORE
GET IN TOUCH
CONTACT US
Contact Form
845-878-4100
137 Birch Hill Rd.Patterson, NY 12563
QUICK LINKS
Hours
